Register of the Herbert Hoover subject collection, 1895-2006
Hoover Institution Archives
- WRITINGS ABOUT HERBERT HOOVER, 1915-1976 (Box 219-229)
  - "The Two Men at the Big Moment," New York Times Magazine, November 6, 1932.
  - "October Ails," by Katherine Dayton, Saturday Evening Post, November 12, 1932.
  - "The Biggest Job in the World," by S.T. Williamson, New York Times Magazine, November 13, 1932.
  - "Realism and Mr. Stimson," by George E. Sokolsky, Vanity Fair, December 1932.
  - "New Year's Day and Mr. Hoover," by Jay Franklin, Vanity Fair, January 1933.
  - "President Hoover as a Latinist: Agricola, a Chapter in the History of Sciences," by Felix Peeters, Revue du Cercle des Alumni de la Fondation Universitaire, extrait du tome IV, no. 3, February 1933.
  - "Herbert Hoover, The Last of the Old Presidents or the First of the New?", by W.A. White., March 4, 1933
  - "President Hoover and the World Depression," by Mark Sullivan, Saturday Evening Post, March 11 and 18, 1933.
  - "Storm Over Washington," by Mark Sullivan, Saturday Evening Post, April 1, 1933. (Box 226)
  - "America's Official Point of View on the Debts," Saturday Evening Post, May 13, 1933.
  - "The Growing Burden of the Presidency," Saturday Evening Post, June 3, 1933.
  - "Visit of Former President Herbert Hoover," Pacific College Bulletin, 1934.
  - "Why It Is Hoover Dam!" by L.W. Bannister, Los Angeles Times, February 18, 1934.
  - "The Strangest President," by Irwin H. Hoover, Saturday Evening Post, April 7, 1934.
  - "News and Comment from the National Capital," Literary Digest, August 1934.
  - "I Do Not Choose," by Irwin H. Hoover, Saturday Evening Post, September 1, 1934.
  - "Enter Franklin Roosevelt," by Ike Hoover, Saturday Evening Post, September 29, 1934.
  - "The Libraries of the Presidents of the United States," American Antiquarian Society, 1935.
  - Drake Alumnus statement that Herbert Hoover would deliver commencement address, May 1935.
  - "Origins of the Banking Panic of March 4, 1933," Saturday Evening Post, June 8, 15, 22 and 29, 1935.
  - "The New Hoover," Collier's, October 12, 1935.
  - "Republicans Must Choose," by John Spargo, Review of Reviews, reprint., December 1935
  - "Has Hoover Changed His Soul?", Liberty, December 14, 1935.
  - Reference to Herbert Hoover, Daily Commercial News, 1936.
  - "Hoover and Roosevelt: A Contrast in Policies," Los Angeles Times, reprint., 1936
  - "Mr. Hoover's Speech at Lincoln," by John Spargo, New York Herald Tribune, reprint., January 20, 1936
  - "Cleveland and Hoover: A Parallel," by John Spargo, New York Herald Tribune, reprint., February 11, 1936
  - "The Legend of Hoover Who 'Did Nothing,'" by John Spargo, March 21, 1936.
  - "Herbert Hoover and His Connection with Burma," Journal Research Society, August 1936.
  - "The Crisis and the Political Parties," Atlantic Monthly, September 1937.
  - "What's Happened to Hoover," by George E. Sokolsky, Commentator, December 1937.
  - "It's Been a Great Show," Collier's, February 12, 1938.
  - "Through Europe with Mr. Hoover, Random Notes, Personal and Confidential," by Perrin C. Galpin., February and March, 1938
  - "Herbert Hoover Looks at Europe," Life, April 11, 1938.
  - "Herbert Hoover as I Knew Him," Opportunity, July 1938.
  - "What America Must Do Next," interview with Will Irwin, Liberty, July 16, 1938.
  - "The Duel with Hoover," by Raymond Moley, Saturday Evening Post, July 8, 1939. (Box 227)
  - "How Foreign Nations Poison Our Minds," by Will Irwin, Liberty, October 28 and November 4, 1939.
  - "Campaign," Time, December 18, 1939.
  - "Hoover's Mistakes," Wallace Miner, May 23, 1940.
  - "The Winner--Famine," by Walter Davenport, Collier's, July 27, 1940.
  - "Herbert Hoover's European Relief Plan," New York Herald Tribune, August and September 1940.
  - "Will Europe Hunger This Winter?" Saturday Evening Post, November 30, 1940.
  - "Let Hoover Feed Them," Collier's, December 28, 1940.
  - "Only America," Time, February 24, 1941.
  - "Hoover, '95, Most Noted Stanfordite," Stanford Daily, May 23, 1941.
  - "Crucified on a Cross of Misunderstanding and Prejudice," Hospitalization News, June 1941.
  - "The Hoover Library," Time, June 30, 1941.
  - "Food Is a Weapon," by Hugh Gibson, Saturday Evening Post, February 21, 1942.
  - "Hunger Spreads over Europe," Working Front, January 1943.
  - "We Asked Mr. Hoover," What's New i n Food and Nutrition, January 1943.
  - "Portrait of Mr. Hoover Unveiled," Stanford Today, September 1944.
  - "Dr. Hoover's Nostrums," by John Stuart, New Masses, April 10, 1945.
  - "The Real Story of Hoover's Foreign Policy," by Bruce Minton, The Worker, April 29, 1945.
  - "A.B.C. Network Interview with Herbert Hoover,", March 12, 1946.
  - "Herbert Hoover, a Tribute," by Vernon Boyce Hampton, March 27, 1946.
  - "The Return of Herbert Hoover,", 1947.
  - "Long Delayed Tribute Paid Herbert Hoover," by George E. Sokolsky, (restoring name to Hoover Dam)., April 1947
  - "Mr. Hoover Gets the Surprise of His Life," by Arthur Krock, New York Times, July 23, 1948.
  - "Herbert Clark Hoover, Patriot," Argonaut, August 5, 1949.
  - "Bonus March Riot Plot Told," Congressional Record, August 31, 1949.
  - "Herbert Hoover's 75th Birthday at Stanford," Stanford Review, September 1949.
  - "Herbert Hoover, Celebrity of the Week," Bill Stern's Sports Newsreel, September 1949.
  - Memorandum concerning the public stature of Herbert Hoover, by Edgar Rickard, October 1949.
  - "The Facts About the Bonus March," by Patrick J. Hurley, McCall's, November 1949.
  - "Herbert Hoover, International Detective," Saturday Evening Post, March 11, 1950.
  - "Granddaddy," by Allan Hoover, May 1951.
  - "This Above All, a Vignette of Herbert Hoover," by Arthur Kemp, August 1951.
  - "The Youth of an Ex-President," New Leader, November 21, 1951.
  - "Herbert Hoover - The Friend of All Mankind," by Hazel Lyman Nickel, ca. 1952.
  - "Herbert Hoover," Time, June 23, 1952.
  - "Herbert Hoover: Man and Statesman," by Virgil M. Hancher, August 10, 1954.
  - "The Philosophy of Herbert Hoover," Los Angeles Times, November 27, 1954.
  - "Address by Ward Bannister About Herbert Hoover,", May 1955.
  - Tribute to Mr. Hoover by Hon. James A. Farley, June 1955.
  - "Laying Foundation Stones," by Ralph Arnold, Historical Society of Southern California Quarterly, June 1955.
  - "Herbert Hoover and High Blood Pressure," Life and Health, January 1956.
  - "Herbert Hoover and the Federal Farm Board Project, 1921-1925," by James H. Shideler, March 1956.
  - "To Promote Peace, a Tour of Hoover Library," Collier's, August 17, 1956.
  - "Herbert Hoover's Grundsaetze zur Bewertung einer Lagerstaette," Zeitschrift fuer Angewandte Geologie, 1957. (Box 228)
  - "Herbert Hoover's Operation Pack Rat," by Frank J. Taylor, Reader's Digest, June 1957.
  - "Sure Cure for Stage Fright," Saturday Evening Post, September 14, 1957.
  - "What Herbert Hoover Has Done for Stanford University," by Bernice Miller, November 1957.
  - "Herbert Hoover and the End of a Mission," Newsweek, 1958.
  - "Home of the Thirty-First President," Ford Times, June 1958.
  - "Hoover Home in Palo Alto," Palo Alto, June 18, 1958.
  - "Herbert Hoover's Contagious Courage," by William Vance, American Mercury, December 1958.
  - "Herbert Hoover, a Birthday Salute," American Weekly, August 9, 1959.
  - "The Liquidation of Herbert Hoover," Reader's Digest, May 1960.
  - "Bread upon the Waters," by E.M. Holiday, American Heritage, August 1960.
  - "Herbert Hoover, the Chief," by William E. Hall, 1961.
  - "Herbert Hoover Reaches 87," by David Brown, Sunday Magazine, August 6, 1961.
  - "A Birthday Letter to Herbert Hoover," by Lewis Strauss, Reader's Digest, August 10, 1961.
  - "Stanford University and Herbert Hoover: Fifty Years a Trustee," by Rita Ricardo-Campbell, typescript draft, March 14, 1962.
  - "Yours Faithfully, Herbert Hoover," Reader's Digest, August 1962.
  - "Happy Birthday, Herbert Hoover," by Ben Hibbs, Saturday Evening Post, August 1962.
  - "Hoover in Iowa," The Palimpsest, August 1962.
  - "We Fed Our Enemies," CBS program, February 17, 1963.
  - "The Ordeal of Herbert Hoover," by Carl Degler, Yale Review, June 1963.
  - Article about Herbert Hoover, Consulting Engineer, August 1963.
  - "Much Maligned Herbert Hoover Wins the Hearts of the People," by Ruth Nathan, March 1, 1964.
  - "Sound Biography of Herbert Clark Hoover," Radio Liberty program, June 9, 1964.
  - "My First Eighty Years," by Harry S. Truman, Saturday Evening Post, June 13, 1964.
  - "Memoir of a Mission, A.R.A. and Herbert Hoover in the U.S.S.R., 1921-1923," by Henry C. Wolfe, Saturday Review, June 13, 1964.
  - "Six Campaigns to Remember," This Week, San Francisco Chronicle, June 17, 1964.
  - "New York World's Fair, 1964-65," Holiday, July 1964.
  - "From Herbert Hoover on His 90th Birthday," Reader's Digest, September 1964.
  - Press release from the Office of the President's Committee for Traffic Safety, October 22, 1964.
  - "Hoover and Historians, Final Judgment Awaited," by David Lawrence, New York Herald Tribune, October 23, 1964.
  - "Herbert C. Hoover," by Julian S. Myrick, November 1964.
  - "Individual Faithfulness," by Henry J. Cadbury, Friends' Journal, November 11, 1964.
  - "How Bert Hoover Met Lou Henry," Stanford Review, November-December 1964.
  - "Herbert Hoover Biography," Reader's Digest, December 1964. (Box 229)
  - "Virtue Is the Doing," by Carol Green Wilson, Stanford Review, January-February 1965.
  - "Herbert Hoover, Engineer," by Frederick E. Terman, Science, January 1965.
  - "Hoover Called Outstanding Applied Scientist," by Frederick E. Terman, The Idaho Professional Engineer, February 1965.
  - "Herbert Clark Hoover," by Lewis L. Strauss, August 1965.
  - "My Visit with Herbert Hoover," by Cyril Clemens, Hobbies, April 1966.
  - "Herbert Hoover and Education," by Raymond H. Muessig, School and Society, 1967.
  - "Herbert C. Hoover," Columbus Dispatch, February 5, 1967.
  - "31st President Draws High Praise," Columbus Dispatch Magazine, February 19, 1967.
  - "Herbert Hoover Left Imprint," Palo Alto Times, January 30, 1968.
  - "Herbert Hoover, 1874-1964, Another Appraisal," by Joseph S. Davis, 1969.
  - "Herbert Hoover, a Personal Sketch," by Ray Lyman Wilbur, n.d.
  - "Herbert Hoover, Where He Has Spent His Life, 1874-1919,", n.d.
  - "Herbert Hoover, Who He Is and What He Has Done,"
  - "High Lights in the Hoover Administration," New Jersey Republican, n.d.
  - "Hoover Defends the New Tariff Law," Politics
  - "Hoover Picks His Men," by William Hard, Review of Reviews, n.d.
  - "Life in Washington,", n.d.
  - "Mr. Hoover, the Mud Washed Away," by Bert Collier, n.d.
  - "President and People Govern Together," by Ellis A. Yost, League of Republican Women
  - Chapter 24 about Herbert Hoover, Song of America by George Mardikian.
  - "True Greatness, the Story of the Quaker President by a Quaker," by Ruth Milhous.
  - "Why Not Hoover?", by C.E. Bratten.
  - Reviews of works about Herbert Hoover.
    - Bane, Suda, and Ralph Lutz, editors, The Blockade of Germany.
    - Irwin, Will, Herbert Hoover.
    - Kellogg, Vernon, Herbert Hoover.
    - Lochner, Louis, Herbert Hoover and Germany.
    - Lyons, Eugene, The Herbert Hoover Story.
    - McGee, Dorothy, Herbert Hoover.
    - Warren, Harris Gaylord, Herbert Hoover and the Great Depression.
    - Miscellaneous.
- CLIPPINGS, PRESS SUMMARIES, AND PRESS RELEASES, 1897-1969 (Box 230-295)
  Newspaper and magazine clippings, press summaries, press releases, and scrapbooks about Herbert Hoover, arranged in chronological order.
  - Scrapbook of clippings and printed matter, concerning Herbert Hoover and mining, 1897-1904. (Box 230)
  - 1913-1916. (Box 231)
  - Hoover as candidate in 1920 election., 1916-1919
  - January 1 -July 31, 1917.
  - August 1, 1917 - August 31, 1919. (Box 232)
  - January 1 - August 31, 1919. (Box 233)
  - Conditions in Europe., January - July 1919
  - Conditions in Europe., August - December 1919 (Box 234)
  - September 1919.
  - October - December 1919. (Box 235)
  - Anti-Hoover politics., 1920
  - Foreign press coverage of U.S. politics., 1920
  - John Maynard Keynes, "How to Mend the Treaty.", January 21, 1920
  - January 1920.
  - January - February 1920. (Box 236)
  - March 1920. (Box 237)
  - Hoover as Presidential candidate., March 1920
  - Hoover as Presidential candidate., March 1920 (Box 238)
  - April 1-10, 1920.
  - April 18-30, 1920. (Box 239)
  - May 1920. (Box 240)
  - "The Hoover Republican.", May 3, 1920
  - Republican Convention., June 1920
  - June 1920.
  - July - December 1920. (Box 241)
  - scrapbook., March - May 1921
  - April - May 1921. (Box 242)
  - July - August 1921. (Box 243)
  - September 1921. (Box 244)
  - October - December 1921. (Box 245)
  - December 1921. (Box 246)
  - February 1922.
  - November 1922.
  - December 1922.
  - December 1922. (Box 247)
  - miscellaneous., 1923
  - April 1923.
  - April 1923. (Box 248)
  - July - August 1923. (Box 249)
  - miscellaneous., 1924
  - attitude of press toward Hoover., February - June 1924 (Box 250)
  - 1925.
  - miscellaneous., 1927
  - miscellaneous., 1928
  - Lou Henry Hoover biographies., 1928
  - "The Life of Herbert Hoover," New York Telegram, biographical series., 1928
  - magazine articles., 1928
  - January - February 1928. (Box 251)
  - political cartoons., February 1928
  - March 1928.
  - political cartoons., March 1928 (Box 252)
  - April 1928.
  - political cartoons., April - May 1928
  - May - June 15, 1928.
  - June 16-30, 1928. (Box 253)
  - political cartoons., July - December 1928
  - July - November 1928.
  - Foreign press coverage., December 1928. (Box 254)
    - Australia, New Zealand.
    - Canada.
    - Caribbean.
    - Ceylon.
    - China.
    - England.
    - Miscellaneous.
    - South America, reports of Hoover's tour of South America, arranged chronologically. (Box 255)
      - La Nueva Prensa, Costa Rica., November 28, 1928
      - La Provincia, Chile., December 6, 1928
      - La Prensa, Buenos Aires, Argentina., December 9, 1928
      - El Diario Ilustrado, El Imparcial, El Mercurio, La Nacion, Chile., December 10, 1928
      - La Prensa, El Telegrafo, El Universo, Ecuador., December 10, 1928
      - El Diario Ilustrado, El Mercurio, La Nacion, Chile., December 11, 1928
      - La Nacion, Buenos Aires, Argentina., December 11, 1928
      - Buenos Aires Herald, La Prensa, The Standard, Buenos Aires, Argentina., December 11, 1928
      - Buenos Aires Herald, La Nacion, La Prensa, The Standard, Buenos Aires, Argentina., December 12, 1928 (Box 256)
      - Buenos Aires Herald, La Prensa, The Standard, Buenos Aires, Argentina., December 13, 1928
      - La Nacion, Buenos Aires, Argentina., December 13, 1928
      - Tilma, Buenos Aires, Argentina., December 14, 1928
      - Buenos Aires Herald, The Standard, Buenos Aires, Argentina., December 14, 1928
      - Buenos Aires Herald, The Standard, Tilma, Buenos Aires, Argentina., December 15, 1928
      - El Dia, La Tribuna Popular, Montevideo, Uruguay., December 16, 1928
      - El Dia, El Diario, El Ideal, Imparcial, El Pais, El Plata, Montevideo, Uruguay., December 17, 1928
      - Journal do Brasil, Rio de Janeiro, Brasil., December 21, 1928
      - Correio da Manha, O Journal, Rio de Janeiro, Brasil., December 22, 1928
      - O Paiz, Rio de Janeiro, Brasil., December 23, 1928
  - 1929. (Box 257)
    - Foreign press.
    - American press, arranged chronologically.
      - No month.
      - January.
      - February.
      - March.
      - April.
      - May.
      - June.
      - July.
      - August.
      - September.
      - October.
      - November.
      - December.
  - 1930.
    - No month.
    - January.
    - February.
    - March.
    - April.
    - May.
    - June.
    - July.
    - August.
    - September.
    - October.
    - November.
    - December.
  - 1931.
    - No month.
    - January.
    - February.
    - March.
    - April.
    - May. (Box 258)
    - June.
    - July.
    - August.
    - September.
    - October.
    - November.
    - December.
  - 1932.
    - Campaign cartoons.
    - No month.
    - January.
    - February.
    - March.
    - April.
    - May.
    - June.
    - July.
    - August.
    - September.
    - October. (Box 259)
    - November.
    - December.
  - 1933.
    - Hoover.
    - Roosevelt administration.
  - 1934.
    - Hoover.
    - Roosevelt administration.
  - 1935. (Box 260)
    - Hoover.
    - Roosevelt administration.
  - 1936.
  - 1937.
  - 1938. (Box 261)
    - American press.
    - European press, reports of Hoover's tour, arranged chronologically.
      - No day, Aktuality Tydne, Czechoslovakia, News from Poland, YMCA, Poland.
      - La Depeche, Echo du Nord, Grand Echo du Nord de la France, Le Reveil du Nord, France., February 25, 1938
      - Prager Tageblatt, Czechoslovakia., March 2, 1938
      - Narodni Politika, Czechoslovakia., March 3, 1938
      - A-Zet, The Central European Observer, Ceske Slovo, Ceskoslovensky Zemedelec, Lidove Noviny, Lidovy Denik, Narodni Noviny, Narodni Osobozeni, Czechoslovakia., March 4, 1938
      - A-Zet, Bohemia, Ceske Slovo, Lidove Noviny, Lidovy Denik, Narodni Listy, Czechoslovakia., March 5, 1938
      - Narodni Osvobozeni, Narodni Noviny, Narodni Politika, Narodni Stred, Prager Presse, Prager Tageblatt, Ranni Noviny, Prazske vydani Narod, Prazske Narod, Prazsky Narod, Prazsky Kuryr, Venkov, Czechoslovakia., March 5, 1938 (Box 262)
      - Bohemia, Ceskoslovenska Rodina, Lidove Noviny, Narodny Listy, Narodni Politika, Czechoslovakia., March 6, 1938
      - Correspondance Politique, Austria., March 9, 1938
      - Kurjer Warszawski, Russkoe Slovo, Poland., March 10, 1938
      - Kurier Poznanski, Kurier Warszawski, Poland., March 11, 1938
      - The Baltic Times, Czas, Express Poranny, Gazeta Polska, Ilustrowany Kuryer Codzienny, Kurjer Warszawski, Polska Zbrojna, Poland., March 12, 1938
      - Ilustrowany Kuryer Codzienny, Poland., March 13, 1938 (Box 263)
      - Helsingin Sanomat, Finland., March 14, 1938
      - Helsingin Sanomat, Hufvudstadbladet, Svenska Pressen, Uusi Suomi, Finland., March 15, 1938
  - miscellaneous., 1930s-1940s (Box 264)
  - January - May 1940.
  - June - December 1940.
  - Republican National Convention., 1940
  - 1941.
  - 1942. (Box 265)
  - Landon - Hoover, Moscow Conference., 1943 (Box 266)
  - 1943-1945.
  - January - June 1945. (Box 267)
  - June 15 - July 1945. (Box 268)
  - August - October 1945. (Box 269)
  - November 1945 - February 1946. (Box 270)
  - March 1946. (Box 271)
  - March 14-31, 1946. (Box 272)
  - April 1946. (Box 273)
  - April 20-30, 1946. (Box 274)
  - May 1-14, 1946. (Box 275)
  - May 15-22, 1946. (Box 276)
  - foreign press coverage of Hoover's trip to Central and South America., May - June 1946 (Box 277)
    - Excelsior, Mexico., May 27, 1946
    - Panama American, Panama., May 29, 1946
    - El Comercio, La Prensa, Lima, Peru., June 1, 1946
    - El Comercio, La Cronica, Journada, Lima, Peru., June 2, 1946
    - La Prensa, La Tribuna, Lima, Peru., June 2, 1946
    - El Comercio, La Cronica, La Prensa, La Tribuna, Lima, Peru., June 3, 1946
    - El Comercio, La Cronica, La Prensa, Lima, Peru., June 4, 1946 (Box 278)
    - Buenos Aires Herald, Argentina, El Diario Ilustrado, Chile, El Mercurio, Chile., June 6, 1946
    - La Nacion, Chile, La Razon, Buenos Aires, Argentina, The Standard, Buenos Aires, Argentina., June 6, 1946
    - Buenos Aires Herald, La Epoca, La Nacion, Buenos Aires, Argentina., June 7, 1946
    - La Esfera, Caracas, Venezuela., June 18, 1946
    - The Havana Post, Information, El (Nuevo) Mundo, Cuba., June 19, 1946
  - May 23 - June 16, 1946. (Box 279)
  - June 17 - July 15, 1946. (Box 280)
  - July 16 - August 19, 1946. (Box 281)
  - August 20 - September 30, 1946. (Box 282)
  - October 1946. (Box 283)
  - November 1946. (Box 284)
  - June 1947.
  - 1947-1949. (Box 285)
  - Hoover's 75th birthday celebration., 1949
  - miscellaneous., 1950-1959
  - statement to press on the presidential election., November 7, 1952 (Box 286)
  - Hoover's 80th birthday celebration., 1954
  - German press re Hoover visit., November 1954
  - Hoover's 83rd birthday celebration., 1957
  - Hoover's 84th birthday celebration., 1958
  - Miscellaneous.
  - Hoover's 85th birthday celebration., 1959
  - 1960.
    - California in presidential politics.
    - Religious issue in the campaign.
    - Republican Convention.
    - Presidential campaign.
    - Campaign slogans.
    - "As Maine Goes, So Goes the Nation."
    - "Crowds Don't Mean Votes."
    - Kennedy-Nixon debates.
    - Hoover's 86th birthday celebration.
  - 1961. (Box 287)
    - General.
    - Hoover's 87th birthday celebration.
    - Medical education.
    - Germany.
    - Finland.
    - Iowa University.
    - Christmas message.
    - Dedication of Lake Ochochahee.
  - 1962.
    - General.
    - Cuba.
    - Hoover's 88th birthday celebration.
    - Presidential Library celebration, West Branch, Iowa. (Box 288)
    - President Kennedy's speech at Yale.
    - President Kennedy.
    - Constitutional Convention.
    - Hoover, miscellaneous.
    - Hoover's operation.
    - Greenup Dam, Ohio.
  - 1963.
    - General.
    - Children.
    - Constitution and religious freedom.
    - Freedoms Foundation.
    - Kennedy administration.
    - Hoover, miscellaneous. (Box 289)
    - Hoover's 89th birthday celebration.
    - Editorial and magazine articles. (Box 290)
    - Hoover administration.
    - Hoover Presidential Library.
  - 1964.
    - Hoover's 90th birthday celebration.
    - January - September.
    - Reports of Hoover's death. Newspaper clippings, arranged by state., October - December.
      - General.
      - Alabama.
      - Arkansas.
      - California.
        - General.
        - Los Angeles. (Box 291)
        - Palo Alto.
          - General.
          - Palo Alto Times.
        - San Francisco.
      - Colorado
      - Connecticut.
      - Delaware.
      - Florida.
      - Georgia.
      - Hawaii.
      - Indiana.
      - Idaho.
      - Illinois. (Box 292)
      - Iowa.
      - Kansas.
      - Kentucky.
      - Louisiana.
      - Maine.
      - Massachusetts.
      - Michigan.
      - Minnesota.
      - Mississippi.
      - Missouri. (Box 293)
      - Montana.
      - Nebraska.
      - Nevada.
      - New Jersey.
      - New York.
        - General.
        - New York Times.
      - North Carolina.
      - Ohio.
      - Oklahoma.
      - Oregon.
      - Pennsylvania. (Box 294)
      - Rhode Island.
      - South Carolina.
      - South Dakota.
      - Tennessee.
      - Texas.
      - Utah.
      - Vermont.
      - Virginia.
      - Washington.
      - Washington, D.C.
      - West Virginia.
      - Wisconsin.
      - Wyoming.
  - 1965. (Box 295)
    - Miscellaneous.
    - Hoover's 91st birthday commemoration.
  - Hoover's 93rd birthday commemoration., 1967
  - 1966-1968.
  - 1969.
  - Miscellaneous clippings.
- EDITORIAL ANALYSES, 1928-1933 (Box 296-312)
  Summary analyses of editorial comment made by various newspapers on selected political issues and subjects during the Hoover administration, arranged alphabetically by subject. Analyses list types of editorial comments made, titles of newspapers analyzed, circulation statistics for each newspaper, and date of editorial comments. A detailed index to the analyses is contained in box number 296.
  - Analyses of positions taken by newspapers on selected issues, arranged by newspaper. (Box 296)
  - General subject index to analyses by subject.
  - Adams, Secretary, Annual Report, 1931.
  - Antarctica territorial dispute following Byrd Expedition.
  - Babson, Robert, statement on Senate's contribution to national security and confidence, November 1929.
  - Bank Deposit Guarantee Bills, Glass Bill, April 1932.
  - Bankers and Industrialists' Reconstruction Committee, May 1932.